CONTACT INFO

Cell: 0030 6983931901

Email: grigorisg3jobs@hotmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/grigoris-palaiochoritis/

GitHub: https://github.com/GrigorisPs Portfolio: https://grigorisps.github.io/



GRIGORIS PALAIOCHORITIS
ENTRY LEVEL FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Being a career changer, I recently graduated from **PeopleCert Education Coding Bootcamp (Javascript)**. For the past 3 years I have been self-employed, providing food and drink services as a cafe owner. Running my own business, helped me build good sense of responsibility and multitasking was part of my everyday job. In order to stay competitive I had to be a fast learner and be motivated by setting new goals

EDUCATION

Oct 2020 - Apr 2021 AFDEmp PeopleCert Education Full Stack Development

- 500 hrs of intensive training in Software Development
- Object Oriented Programming, Functional Programming, Debugging Techniques, Test Driven Development, Common Architecture Patterns, Data/Class Modelling

CERTIFICATIONS

PeopleCert Software Developer Skills (Foundation Level) PeopleCert Software Developer Skills (Advanced Level)

LANGUAGES

Greek - Native English - B2

SKILLS

- HTML5,Css,Bootstrap,TailwindCss,JavaScript,Typescript,jquery
- Web MVC,Node.Js,Express.js ReactJs, Angular
- SQL MySQL, PostGre
- Git, XML, RESTful API

PROJECTS

Individual Projects

Netflix-clone - Weatherapp - Aurora Grove

- NextJs, ReactJs, Javascript, Typescript
- Firebase, Auth, Stripe
- REST routes, HTTP status codes
- HTML, CSS, TailwindCss, Bootstrap

Group Project

VideoClub - eBook

User signup - login

- Different user roles
- Ability to connect to a database
- Product filtering
- Real-time chat socketIO
- Payment process PayPal checkout (sandbox)
- Sails.js
- Sass

CAREER SUMMARY

Self-Employed Cafe Owner

Old Villager | May 2019 - January 2023

System Administrator Assistant

Wizznet Station | Apr 2018 - May 2019

Military obligations fullfilled